RESUME. 2023

Thanawit Kaniwaranon

(+66)97-075-5663

CONTACT ME

kt.thanawit@gmail.com www.yourwebsite.com

WEBSITE DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

2020 - 2022: King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi

Master of Science in Digital Business Information System

GPAX: 3.35

2014 - 2018 : Kasetsart University Kamphaeng Saen Campus

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

GPAX: 2.65

SKILLS

Front-end Development: Back-end Development:

Vue.js Node.js Bootstrap Nest.js

jQuery Spring Boot

JavaScript

PHP

ABOUT ME

I am a software developer proficient in JavaScript and Vue Framework, with experience working in teams and as an independent worker. I am able to learn and adapt to new technologies and am ready to collaborate with your team to develop better software for the future.

WORK EXPERIENCES

2022 - present: COREWISDOM Co., Ltd.

(part of the CDG group)

Programmer Analyst

- Analyzed user requirements, developed understanding of functionality needed in software systems by working closely with clients.
- Designed and developed efficient software solutions using programming languages and software development tools.
- Maintained and upgraded software systems to ensure efficiency and effectiveness for clients.

2018 - 2022 : CORE SOLUTIONS co.,Ltd.

(part of the CDG group)

Front-end Developer

- Designed and developed responsive web pages and user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Optimized website performance and load times through code optimization
- Maintain and update existing web pages and user interfaces to ensure they are compatible across multiple platforms.